and now at hip-hop news break with Chuck
[Music]
Taylor
it's been a very busy day in the news a
lot of things have happened a Staten
Island man is listed in stable condition
tonight after a brutal assault by rapper
Method Man following an argument the
victim addressed the press earlier today
it was torture straight towards his son
first he put my nuts on the dresser
it was crazy just my nuts and then he
banged him with a spike fat super
handsome she kept feed and feed me baby
this all took place in slums of Shaolin
it was the RZA the GZA old Dirty Bastard
Raekwon the chef u-god Inspectah deck
and of course
Method Man victim also said that at one
point during the altercation Method Man
put a hanger on the stove and left it
for like 40 minutes and then he stuck it
in his ass real slow
at this point Method Man is still at
large so stay tuned to News Channel 3
for this and other stories
[Applause]